got us, George.
>> Yes, sir. That's better.
>> Hey, Joy, did you plan this to happen at
halftime with the CO?
>> Yeah, he just texted me. Um, we wasn't
able to talk, but I know he's proud of
me.
>> Hey, I know you've had a pretty eventful
pre-draft process. Just, you know, what
does it feel like now to have it all
wrapped up and to be a New Orleans
Saint?
>> Yeah, it feels great. Shoot. I I never
stopped working. So, I was cool with it.
I never stopped working out. Never got
out of shape. Never had to restart my
soreness process. Never had to get my
feet counted back up. So, shoot. I'm
ready to hit the ground running right
now.
>> Jordan, did did you uh get to meet Chris
Lave on on your visit?
>> For sure. Yeah. He sat in our meeting
with Coach Dub. Um we talked on the
phone a couple of times. So, for sure.
Yeah, that's my dog. We we locked in and
should be ready to work.
>> What do you like about his game?
>> Uh he's different. He can do it all.
He's he's a speedster, so he can take
you over the top, but at the same time,
he can settle it down just as fast. So,
he he can do anything and everything at
the position. He play slide. He can play
outside. He's kind of like me, but um
but he's proven himself. say that.
>> What do you think about playing
alongside a lot of
>> Oh, it's going to be amazing. Shoot. Um
take pressure off each other, make make
our jobs easier, and shoot. I feel like
um us oneonone shooting.
>> It's going to get ugly.
>> What can you bring What do you bring to
the table?
>> Say that again.
>> What can you bring to the Saints?
>> Um just uh versatility. I feel like just
just another playmaker in the room. I
feel like a guy that you come to on
third down is that's always going to be
open in a sense. So just just just
playmaking ability and then um just a
just a guy that's always in the
building, always guys trying to meet new
teammates, see see where their story
came from and just pouring into guys,
love on guys and I feel like yeah,
that's what I bring.
>> Know about Shup right now? Like what do
you know about his game? How would you
describe his game?
>> He's a great quarterback. He played half
the season and he finished finalist in
offensive rookie of the year. So great
player. He's going to continue to do big
things. He's very smart. He knows how to
read the defense. Always on time. He's a
he's a great quarterback. Came with to
get to work with him.
>> Jordan, what triggered your emotions?
>> Um, it's just just where I came from.
Like, I wasn't supposed to be here. I
was 5'4 my sophomore year. I had no work
ethic until my junior year. It was I'm
not supposed to be here without without
God blessing me with an amazing family,
an amazing support system, and just God
bringing me the right people in my in my
circle. I wouldn't be here. So, it's
it's all credit to God and just what he
did with with my life and all the people
around me. What? How does it feel that
you'll get to play so close to home
being a Texas native?
>> It's amazing. Um, sure. I can go back
home whenever I need. My brother has a
house in Dallas, so I got a spot to stay
there, but um, it's amazing. I'm ready
to get to work. I'm ready to get back to
the South. I've been on the West Coast
too long.
>> What changes with your work ethic your
junior year?
>> Um, my brother just shoot me to the to
the weight room one time and shoot, I
decided that's what I want to do instead
of playing the video game. It was all my
brother. I just
I just I just tagged along with him and
he brought me a lifetime. We had
Lifetime Fitnesses on passes and that's
all we used to do every day.
>> Hey Jordan, a lot's been uh talked about
when it comes to your injury history and
things like that. What would you like to
clear up about that or or say about you
know your process?
>> I'm going to give myself the best
opportunity to stay on the field and be
as healthy as possible. I'm going to do
everything in the weight room. I'm going
do everything in nutrition. I'm going
have my own chef. I'm going to get my
massage on the same day every week.
I'mma have my regimen so down to a tea
that there's I'm gonna give myself the
best opportunity. We do play football,
but I'm gonna give myself the best shot
possible.
>> Is that something you've talked about
with other players before? Like is that
why you have that so locked down
already? Like other players about
>> war?
>> Did you have more interaction with the
Saints than maybe some other teams? And
how would you describe the way the
interaction with the Saints has gone
over the last couple of months?
>> Yeah, they they was trying to get under
my skin. And that's that's how I kind of
knew they was really thinking about it,
really um actually seeing if they was
going to take a chance with me. So, they
was trying to get under my skin. They
trying to see see what I say in
response.
>> Like what? What do you mean?
>> Um we was at the combine. He was like he
had told me something but it wasn't the
truth. Trying to see if I was going to
agree with it and I kind of just didn't
agree with it cuz it wasn't the truth.
>> Who's he? Who are you talking about?
>> For 10 years.
Jordan. Jordan, when did you say to
yourself during your college career that
you would be in this position to be a
first round?
>> To be honest, I feel like
>> this I keep I just keep getting better.
That's all I can say. Like I keep
getting better. I just want to continue
on that track. Uh work works. I'm just
going to continue to work and shoot.
Yeah, that's all I can say. I'm going
just continue to get better, continue to
learn, continue to soak in, take as many
pictures as I possibly can, and just be
the best player and give my put my best
foot forward. Hey Joey, how big was this
night just for you and your family with
this going on and the uh game three
going on?
>> Yeah, it's crazy. My brother had hit a
three right after the Saints had called
me. It was it was like a dream come
true. Um um yeah, it's it's amazing just
having a brother that's playing in the
NBA and playing in the NFL. He just was
the blueprint for me. So, it's it's
everything to us. Um I know my parents
are super super duper happy. They feel
like they can have a little sigh of
relief now, I'm guessing. And yeah, we
we just ready to go. We we we a
close-knit family. Um, it's just us.
Like, we don't have too many outsiders.
Just it's just us. We're gonna pour
everything into the Saints. Um, and
yeah, we're all gonna put our best foot
forward.
>> What do you know about the city of New
Orleans? Have you been here before?
>> To be honest,
to be honest, even even being a neighbor
state in Texas, but um I know I know the
food is real good. I know we ride on the
water. I know it's the South. So, you
going to have the same people uh similar
people as we did in Dallas. But, um Oh,
yeah. Y'all have some great players over
there. Michael Thomas. Y'all had Alva
Kamar for a long stretch. Y'all just got
Travis Ten, who's a great player. Been
following him. So, I'm I'm ready to get
hit the ground running. We have a great
offense and I think we can do some
special teams, especially in our
division.
>> What's your favorite food from
Louisiana?
>> Um, we had went to um the little oyster
spot. It was it was fire. Oh my go
probably hadund 100 oysters.
Jordan, did you say you were 5'4 as a
junior in high school?
>> I was 5'4 as a sophomore in high school
and then I developed a work ethic in my
junior year.
>> So, like when did this actually become
like a reality for you? Like the idea of
of NFL playing career?
>> Yeah, obviously like we was we was going
to try the football thing. Like I've
never known myself without a football.
So, we knew we was going to try it. See
if I can go to college for free. But to
be honest, it didn't hit till
>> probably the end the end of the season.
this season to be honest. I feel like I
just, like I said, I just continue to
get better and I feel like I just want
to stay on that track. I just want to
continue to take my off seasonason so
serious and yeah, be the be the best
player I can be.
>> Tell you said you could tell when it was
that the Saints interest was real in
you. How real was your interest in this
team?
>> Oh, very real. Um, I knew I knew they
had a quarterback. That was that was a
big thing. And then also a receiver on
the other side, a great receiver on the
other side I can learn from and to see
how he handles his business. So it's
it's like a match made in heaven and
we're we're the Saints. So that's that's
>> Jordan. What was it like being coached
by Hines Lord?
>> It it was amazing. Um he he was
everything to me. He played 14 years in
this league. So he's made every snake.
He made every right decision and he just
throughout that he gained knowledge and
wisdom and he just poured all that into
me.
>> Hey Jordan, what was kind of your
mindset when you after your freshman
year when you you know you left
Colorado?
>> Um I just I just knew like
I played my freshman year obviously so I
had some film. I knew I was going to get
more offers than I had out of high
school. So I just knew I had to keep
working. Like that's all my brother
would preach to me. Just hard work,
discipline, continue to be who you say
you want to be. Like just keep going,
man. You and anything's possible through
Christ.
>> Jordan, you said all the things you plan
to do to to work on your health. Was
there anything that you identified
during the process? I know sometimes
guys who have had a hamstring issue,
there was just a story about like
Jackson figuring out any shoe size or
anything that that that's controllable
for you.
>> Yeah, my hips were tight. My hips were
super tight, but I was so strong in the
hips that I would just overcompensate
for the tightness. So, I've been getting
my hips real loose. I don't think it was
really a hamstring problem. It was
probably a hip problem or my glutes
wasn't activating. So, we're working on
like the the whole because it's all
connected. So, we're working on
everything. We're not just working on
the hamstrings. So, I feel like we got a
good sense. I got a good team behind me
and yeah, we're we're ready to go. I
feel like we've been preparing for a
couple months now and yeah, I think I'm
the readyest I'm going to be.
>> How do you feel like you handled
handled, you know, going through that
knowing that it might delay your NFL
dream or I mean like how did you handle
that adversity of the injury?
>> Um, you talking about the knee injury?
Well, I guess like when you had another
one last year that that maybe missed
some games and and some testing time.
Did you like how how did you hand like
you know uh
>> I don't I don't try to look too much
into the future. I try to take each day
for what it is and try to not too many
challenges in one day to to be worried
about the next one. So just like I said,
bro, continue to put your best foot
forward. Work your tail off.
>> When did you hit your growth first?
>> Junior year. I grew to six foot.
Hey, uh, talk to your old your old
quarterback about following him to
Louisiana.
>> Yeah, he text me. I gotta text him back
when we get all this phone doing all
this media stuff. That that's that is
real dope. I ain't I didn't realize
that.
>> Are you ready to tackle the humidity
here in Jan?
>> I'm from the south, man. That ain't that
ain't nothing.
>> It's a different heat.
>> Yeah, it is. It is. It's dry in Arizona.
It's real real dry. You under the shade,
you fine. You can't run from that heat
in in the south. But I'm ready. Is
Louisiana hotter than Texas or about the
same?
>> Is that humidity a little different?
>> Yeah, humidity is a little different.
>> Yeah, because you water
you saying that you grew 8 in from your
sophomore year to your junior year.
>> Yes, sir.
>> My brother was always super tall and my
feet was always super big, so we knew I
had a chance.
What stood out to you about your um
>> your top 30 visit with the Saints?
>> Um it it was everything. Everybody was
cool. Everybody was real about their
business. Like Coach Dub, he he's not
going to play around with me. He's going
to he's going to give me his all. He's
going to um get on my butt when I need
it and it's going to be my biggest fan
at the same time. So just how serious
they are about winning football games.
And I feel like they're on the right
right track and we're ready to turn this
thing around. But I don't think I don't
think it's too bad. So I don't think
it's too much turnaround, but we're
going to be just fine.
>> As this draft was starting tonight, did
you think like was this one of the spots
that you thought this could be my spot
at eight to the Saints? Was this one of
the ones that like you had an asterk by
this might be me?
>> For sure. Um, for sure. Yeah. Yeah, for
sure. I knew I knew it was like 5 to 11,
but yeah, I knew I knew this was for
sure. Just just based off the top 30
interviews, just based on how they was
uh treating me and how they was talking
to me. So definitely knew it was a spot
that could happen. when you didn't go at
five, it's like when you didn't go at
five, did you start to get nervous or
wonder when your name was called or were
you able to was the having the Cavs game
helpful? Like what kind of going through
your mind there?
>> Um I I was I was chilling. I know I know
God has a plan. So no need to worry
anxiety ain't going to do nothing but
make the situation worse.
>> What do you like about Kell Moore's
offense? Um I we briefly went over was
going over the plays at the combine and
uh Dove he was coaching it. He was like
um Pacific Northwest state and I said
Ohio.
He got he got on my tail. He's like no
that's not Pacific Northwest. He was
like Washington. Washington. So I know
um y'all have like different groupings.
I know you have a lot of different um
concepts to the right and to the left.
So I know the quarterback can audible
some stuff if you see stuff you like.
But yeah, I I really like it and I feel
like it's it's going to be nice.
>> What are your impressions of coach do?
>> Let's take a couple more guys.
>> Um, yeah, real real cool dude. Real real
about football. Loves football. He wants
to see the best at his players. He's
going to treat everybody like his like
his sons and I and I was just getting
that feel just off the top 30 visit. So,
I believe he's telling the truth and
yeah, he's going to give me his all for
sure. And I'm ready to go.
>> What did your what goes into making you
such a good route rider? like how how
how did you develop like the detailness
and kind of your suddenness and
everything?
>> I was short. I was short. I was short
playing slot. Um I could only play slot
cuz I was so short and then when I grew
I I just took that slot route running
ability to the outside and yeah just
kind of kept developing, get bigger,
faster, stronger, got my power output up
and sky's the limit. I feel like
>> I think correct me if I'm wrong, your
workout was last week in front of
scouts, right?
>> Yeah. How important was it for you to to
just go out there and show what you do,
show yourself?
>> Um, yeah, it was it was very important.
And I know there was still some some
question marks over my head, but um just
wanted to answer as many as I possibly